我就开门见山直说了
Let's get something straight.
这里  化学  是我的领域
This, the Chemistry, is my realm.
制毒的事归我管
I am in charge of the cooking.
出了这里  外面的事由你处理
Out there on the street, you deal with that.
至于我们那些客户的事
As far as our customers go,
我一点都不想知道
I don't wanna know anything about them
我不想见到他们
I don't want to see them.
也不想听到他们的消息
I don't want to hear from them.
无论如何  我不想跟他们有任何接触
I want no interaction with them whatsoever.
整个行动就你我两人
This operation is you and me,
而我负责幕后的
and I'm the silent partner.
这样安排  你有问题吗
You got any issues with that?
管他什么呢  老兄
Whatever, man.
不管发生什么事
No matter what happens,
不能再有流血事件
No more bloodshed.
不能再用暴力
No violence.
绝
命
毒
师
第一季
第六集
本字幕由YYeTs人人影视翻译制作
更多美剧字幕 请登陆 www.YYeTs.net
■
翻译：joanna    老奶奶    小松狮    夜    缭乱
时间轴：永恒の幻想     特效：Will
■
校对：冰卡      后期：冰河       监制：蛐蛐
-你还好吧  -嗯  没事
- You all right? - Oh, yeah.
我很好
Yeah. I'm okay.
亲爱的  你真的不必...
You know, honey, you really don't have to...
我喜欢呆在这儿陪你
Look, I like being here with you.
我只是说
I'm only saying that,
你想先走的话  我一个人没事的  真的
I'd be okay with it, really, if you want to go.
事实上  如果我知道
You know, actually, it would make me
小沃尔特放学回家的时候
Feel a little better knowing that you were there
你能在那陪着他  会让我更好受些
When Walter Jr. gets home from school.
好吧
Okay.
-你好了就给我打电话吧  -我会的
- You'll call me when you're finished? - Oh, yeah.
你跟埃米利奥联系过了吗
And have you been in touch with Elliott?
因为我还没收到他开来的支票
Because I haven't seen a check from him.
是的  在我这里
Yes, I got it.
-真的  -支票到了  是的
- Really? - It came, yeah.
是的  上周就到了
Yeah, it came last week,
我存进我信用合作社的账户里了  所以
And I put it right into my credit union account, so...
我处理好了
Taken care of it.
很好
Good.
所以说一切都好  一切都好
So we're good. We're good.
周一前先别兑现这张支票  好吗
Could you not deposit this until Monday?
谢谢
Thank you.
如有不适  请及时致电
Call if the discomfort's too much.
不然的话  我们下周再见
Otherwise, we'll see you next week.
好的
Yeah.
化学反应包含两方面的变化
Chemical reactions involve change on two levels:
物质的和能量上的
Matter and energy.
反应逐步发生的时候
When a reaction is gradual,
能量上的变化相当微弱
The change in energy is slight.
你甚至都不会意识到反应的发生
I mean, you don't even notice the reaction is happening.
比方说
For example,
汽车底盘逐步生锈的过程
When rust collects on the underside of a car.
但是如果反应迅速发生
But if a reaction happens quickly,
无害物质则会以某种方式相互作用
Otherwise harmless substances can interact in a way
产生出巨大的能量
That generates enormous bursts of energy.
谁能举个例子来
Who can give me an example
关于快速化学反应
of rapid chemical reaction?
提示一下  看看这里
Hint, Hint. Right here.
比方说  爆炸
Like an explosion?
是的  很好
Yes. Good.
爆炸
Explosions.
爆炸就是由化学反应所致
Explosions are the result of chemical reactions
它几乎在一瞬间发生
Happening almost instantaneously.
爆炸物相互反应的速度越快
And the faster reactants, i.e., explosives,
他们发生变化的速度越快
And fulminative mercury is a prime example of that,
爆炸产生的威力就越大
The faster they undergo change,
雷酸汞就是个最佳的例子
The more violent the explosion.
所以说  爆炸
So... explosions.
好了  大家先从第七章开头
Okay, listen. Why don't you start reading on your own
自己看起来  好吗
From the top of chapter 7,all right?
你还好吧
You okay?
我都知道了  怀特先生
I got it, Mr. White.
别太担心了
Don't worry.
你还有这些孩子要教
You got kids to teach.
谢谢你  雨果
Thanks, Hugo.
他开始日渐消瘦
He's starting to lose weight,
让人看着...
Which is tough...
心里难受
To see that.
当我拥抱他时
You know, to feel the difference
明显感觉到他的变化
when I put my arms around him.
-我能跟他说几句吗  -当然
- Can I talk to him? - Of course.
沃尔特
Walt...
当你不再对我敞开心扉
When you don't let me in
当你不再对我倾述出了什么事
When you don't tell me what's going on,
有时候  我觉得就好像
I think it's like I feel like
你甚至都不想让我陪在你身边
You don't even want me around sometimes.
我没有
No.
还有  最近这些天
And recently these afternoons,
你每天下午都这么晚回家
When you're coming home so late
我们就只能呆在家里  不断想着
And we're just left wondering
你到底去哪了
Where you are.
是的  爸爸
Yeah, Dad.
到底怎么回事
What's up with that?
沃尔特  你还有什么事
Walt, is there anything else
瞒着家里的吗
You're holding back from your family?
是时候说出来了
Now's the time to share.
有时候
I like to be alone,
我就想一个人静一下
I mean at times,
不是针对你们  真的
And it's not about you, really.
只是  有的时候  什么话都不说
It's just that sometimes it feels better
就一个人静静地呆一会
Not to talk at all...
会让我更好受些
About anything, to anyone.
独处  对某些人来说确实会有帮助
Alone time can be helpful for some types.
也许  让你的家人知道
Maybe knowing what you do when you're alone
你独处时都在干嘛
Might make it easier for your family
会让他们更容易理解 也更容易接受
To be more accepting of whatever it is you do alone.
我喜欢下班后散散步
I like to go on walks
一周两次  或者更多
A couple of times a week,maybe more, after work,
我很享受亲近自然
And I really enjoy the nature.
仙人掌
You know, the cacti,
植被之类的
The vegetation, that kind of thing.
这对治疗很有帮助
It's really very therapeutic.
你没事吧
Yo! You okay?
-你吸了那个啥了吗  -没  有点晕而已
- Did you breathe that shit? - No. I'm just dizzy.
起来
Come here.
-坐下  坐下  -热死我了
- Sit down, sit down. - I'm burning up.
把这个脱了吧
Take this off.
坐下  透口气
Sit down. Get some air.
天呐
Oh. God.
就这样  好多了
Yeah, that's better.
你打算什么时候告诉我
When were you going to tell me?
告诉你什么
Tell you what?
癌症
Cancer.
你得了癌症  对吗
You got it, right?
你怎么知道
How did you know?
我姑妈身上也有这种斑点
My aunt had one of those dots on her,
化疗时作指引用的
To target the radiation.
是肺癌吗
What is it, in your lung?
我是你的搭档  你应该跟我说实话
I'm your partner, man. You should have told me.
这个可不酷  一点都不
That's not cool, okay?  Not at all.
到什么阶段了
What stage are you?
中晚期了
3a.
已经扩散到淋巴系统了
Gone to your lymph nodes.
你姑妈
Your aunt.
她查出来的时候到什么程度了
How bad was she when they caught it?
很糟糕  她没撑多久
Bad enough. She didn't last long.
多久
How long?
7个月
Seven months.
我终于明白了
I get it now.
原来你做这些是因为这个
That's why you're doing all this.
你想在临死前为家人留些钱
You want to make some cash for your people before you check out.
-有什么意见吗  -你说呢
- You got a problem with that? - You tell me.
你才像是从微波炉里爬出来的
You're the one that looks like you just crawled out of a microwave.
你能搞定这批货吗
You going to be able to finish the batch?
是的
Yes.
好吧
All right.
不行
No.
你来吧
You do it.
我
Me?
是的
Yeah.
你那些疯狂的绝活都哪儿去了
What happened to your mad skills?
这个  接着
Go on. Here.
你来做
You do it.
你能行的
You can do it.
有什么问题的话  我就在外面
If you have any questions, I'll be right out here.
下次化疗时  在头上放个冰袋
The next time, put an ice pack on your head during chemo.
我姑妈说可以防止脱发
My aunt said it helped with the hair loss.
这是什么  圣诞礼物吗
What's this? Christmas?
这是我们在郊区制毒窝点发现的那个吗
This the one we found way out in the boonies, the cook site?
-该死  -怎么了
- Holy shit. - What?
实验室发现里面有残留的陈旧字迹
Lab pulled up an imprint of some old writing
是马克笔之类的东西写上去的
That used to be on the inside. Old Magic Marker or something.
是吗  写什么了
Yeah? What's it say?
JP怀恩化学实验室所有
"Property of J.P. Wynne Chemistry Lab."
那是沃尔特学校的
That's Walt's school.
说好了3点开始的
We were supposed to start at 3.
我在外面做大买卖的  兄弟  莫急
I'm out there making fat stacks, man. Chill.
预付费手机  拿去用吧
Hey. Prepaid cell phone. Use it.
-这是多少钱  -26张大票子
- How much is this? - 26 big ones.
就这么多  26000美元
Is that all? $26,000?
不  是2600
No, that's 26 hundred,
你的那份是1300
And your share is 13,
再扣除那部手机的25美金
Minus 25 bucks for that phone.
-你卖出去多少冰毒  -差不多1盎司吧
- How much meth did you sell?  - Nearly an ounce.
上次我查的时候
Last time I checked,
足足有一磅[1磅=16盎司]
there were 16 ounces to a pound.
剩下那些都被你吸了吗
You smoked the rest?
整个晚上我都在兜售冰毒
I've been out there all night slinging crystal.
一次1/10磅
You think it's cake
你当是卖蛋糕呢
moving a pound of meth one teenth at a time?
你干嘛这么小量的卖
Why are you selling it in such small quanties?
为什么不把一整磅直接出手
Why don't you just sell the whole pound at once?
卖给谁  你以为我是刀疤脸啊
To who? What do I look like, Scarface?
这可不能接受
This is unacceptable.
我可是在犯罪啊
I am breaking the law here.
这么点钱可不值得冒这么大风险
This return is too little for the risk.
我以为你今天准备再做一磅呢
I thought you'd be ready for another pound today.
或许你很精通化学
You may know a lot about chemistry, man.
但你对贩毒却一窍不通
But you don't know jack about slinging dope.
告诉你吧  我觉得你缺乏动力
Well, I'll tell you, I know a lack of motivation when I see it.
你应该更加发挥想象
You've got to be more imaginative, you know?
打破常规思维
Just think outside the box here.
我们得大量出货
We have to move our product in bulk,
大宗批发
wholesale, now.
怎么才能办到
How do we do that?
-你是说找个大毒枭  -没错
- What do you mean, to a distributor? - Yes. Yes.
我们就需要这个  一个大毒枭
That's what we need. We need a distributor now.
你认识这样的人吗
Do you know anyone like that?
是的  以前认识个  不过被你杀了
Yeah, I mean I used to until you killed him.
谁上了疯狂小八的位
So who took Krazy-8's place?
一个叫Tuco的家伙
Some guy named Tuco.
听说是个十足的混球
A bad ass, from what I hear.
好吧  屠库  去跟屠库谈谈吧
Tuco, okay. So then just go talk to Tuco.
没错
Right.
就像"你好  先生  我知道你不认识我"
Like,"Hello, sir. Hey, I know you don't know me,
你有兴趣入手大量冰毒吗
"But would you be interested in a felony quantity of methamphetamine?"
是的  但是你要用点推销技巧
Well, yes, but maybe with a little more salesmanship, perhaps?
你根本不明白那人是有案底的黑帮分子
You just don't get it, man.  This guy's O.G.
那是什么意思
What does that mean?
拜托  就是说他地位很高
Jesus, look, he's upper level, man.
他不人跟陌生人做生意的
He's not going to do business with some dude he doesn't know.
你不懂这行的规矩
You don't understand the way it works.
你不能就这样冲去找上面贩冰毒的
You can't just bum rush some high-level ice man
抢别人的生意做  懂吗
And start cutting deals, okay?
太冒险了  你得有门路
It's risky. You need an intro.
你得找人做担保
You need someone to vouch.
那谁介绍你认识疯狂小八的
Well, who introduced you to Krazy-8?
埃米利奥  那是因为
Emilio. That's only because
我三年级就认识他了
I knew him from, like, third grade.
我们现在又不能找埃米利奥
We can't talk to Emilio, either... -
好吧  好吧
All right, all right.
听着  怀特老师  这样太冒险了
Look, I'm telling you, Mr. White, it's too risky.
懂吗  我们现在也是在赚钱
Okay? I mean, we're making money.
干嘛你不满足点呢
Why can't you just be satisfied with the way it is?
你就不能TMD胆子大点
Just grow some fucking balls!
还是等到星期一吗
Wait till Monday again?
是的  谢谢
Yes, please. Thank you.
怀特老师
Mr. White.
谢谢你  雨果
Thank you, Hugo.
-咚咚咚  -嘿
- Knock-knock. - Oh, hey.
-沃尔特  感觉怎么样  -很好
- How are you feeling, Walt? - Good.
有人来找你
Are you up for having a visitor?
嘿  伙计
Hey, buddy.
需要什么尽管说
Let me know if you need anything.
我会的  谢谢你  卡门
I will. Thank you, Carmen.
该死
Damn.
这小妞的屁股可真翘
That chick's got an ass like an onion.
真是太正点了
Makes me want to cry.
你来这儿有事吗
So what are you doing here?
我有些问题想问你
Well, I had some questions I wanted to run by you,
关于工作的
Work-related.
你有空吗  待会儿也行
You okay? I could come back later.
不  现在很好
No, no, no, no. I'm fine.
现在很好
Everything's fine.
你说什么和工作有关
What do you mean work-related, though?
你认得这个吗
Do you recognize that?
不认识
No.
这是用来制毒的
That was used to cook meth.
在离这40英里的印第安人地盘上找到
Found that on some Indian land about 40 miles from here.
里面的一个标牌上写着
Old label on the inside used to say...
J.P.怀恩化学实验室
J.P. Wynne Chemistry Lab.
真的吗
Really?
我不知道它是怎么会是这里的
I don't understand how that came from here.
我还希望你能帮我的忙
I was hoping you could help me with that.
我们在一辆弃车旁找到的
We found it near an abandoned car
那车是我们一个线人的
Belonging to one of our snitches.
线人
A snitch?
没错  我们的一个卧底
Yeah, one of our confidential informants.
最近失踪了  还没有人找到他
Went missing a while back. No body yet,
我们肯定他已经
But we're pretty sure he's, you know...
可能被剁成小块喂秃鹰了
Probably chopped up in little pieces and fed to the buzzards.
不管怎样  最近少了防毒面罩吗
Anyway, any respirators like that go missing lately?
不  没有
No. No.
我是说  据我所知没有
No, I mean, not that I know of.
我想看一下仪器清单
I'll need to take a look at that inventory.
没问题  单子就贴在墙上
Sure. I got a list hanging on the wall.
你介意我看一下你的储藏室吗
You mind if I take a look at your storeroom?
当然不  随便看
Not at all, no. Be my guest.
哪些人有这里的钥匙
Right. So who's got keys?
理科教师  校工
Well, the science faculty, the staff,
卡门  副校长也有
Carmen, the vice principal has the master,
还有我
And me.
学生呢
How about students?
不  没有
No, no.
没有学生有这里的钥匙
No students have keys.
我希望也是
I should hope not.
我想问的是有人知道你把这些放在这里吗
My question is do any know where you keep them?
我想没有  没有
I don't think so. No.
而且钥匙我是每天随身带着的  所以
Besides, I keep them right here in my pocket anyway, so...
沃尔特  我知道他们是你的学生
Walt, look, I know they're your students, but,
小看他们  可就大错特错了
Do not underestimate them. Big mistake.
还有别的防毒面罩吗
Are there any other respirators?
呃  没有
Uh, no.
这里只有6个  清单上写着8个
Because I'm counting six. Inventory says eight.
玻璃仪器好像也少了很多
Glassware looking a little sparse.
-有吗  -对
- Is it? - Yeah.
至少缺了几个厄伦美厄细颈瓶
You're missing a couple of Erlenmeyer flasks at least.
哦  对
Oh, yeah.
一个5000毫升的圆底烧瓶
A 5,000 milliliter round bottom.
制毒的家伙们最爱用这个了
Meth heads love to brew in this, baby.
不接吗
Going to answer that?
不  不过是  不接了
No, it's just... No, I don't...
可能是斯凯勒  可能她遇上什么麻烦了
Maybe it's Skyler. She's in trouble or something.
我觉得还是接的好
Don't ignore it on my account.
接吧  我自己能看
Answer it! C'mon, I got stuff to do.
-接吧  -好吧
- Jeez. - Okay.
喂
Hello.
哟  你好吗  W先生
Yo. What's up, Mr. W?
请讲
Speaking.
-不方便说话吗  -当然
- Bad time to talk? - Absolutely.
好吧  那就听我说
All right, so just listen.
知道我们上次说的那个人吧  屠库
You know that guy we were talking about, Tuco?
我朋友瘦子彼得
Turns out my boy Skinny Pete
和他在洛斯鲁纳斯监狱蹲一间板房
Was in the same cellblock with him over at Los Lunas.
我们找到路子了
So we got our in.
我们现在就拿着一磅去找那家伙
We're hauling a pound to the dude right now.
好的
Okay, then.
非常感谢您打来电话
Thank you very much for calling.
我的医生真是热心
My doctor is very solicitous.
听着  兄弟
Look, buddy,
我不想让你惹上麻烦
the last thing I want to do is get you in hot water,
但是有些制毒的家伙很喜欢这里
But some meth monkey had a feeding frenzy in here, okay?
你最好把自己的地盘看紧点
You got to keep a better watch over your turf.
我会的
I will.
我可不想别人怀疑到你头上来  好吗
We don't want people to start wondering about you, right?
没错
Right. No.
没错  当然不想
Right. Absolutely not.
你真和这家伙很铁吗
So you're sure you're tight with this guy?
跟兄弟一样
Two nuts in a ball sack, yo.
伙计  我可是瘦子彼得
Yo, man, I'm Skinny Pete!
也许这主意不怎么好  我们走吧
Maybe this isn't such a good idea, yo. Come on.
伙计  瞧见没
Yo, man. That's what's happening.
屠库要见我们
Yo, Tuco's expecting us.
犯不着  老兄  我和屠库很熟
No need, man. Me and Tuco go back.
屠库  还好吗兄弟
Tuco. What's happening, my brother?
这地方不坏啊
Sick crib, yo.
出来以后混得不赖啊
You been keeping it real since you been sprung.
干多久了  一年
What's it been, like a year?
-你朋友  -对  杰西
- This your boy?  - Yeah, Jesse.
这家伙带了我之前跟你说的东西
The dude with the glass I was telling you about.
久仰
Hey, man. Yeah, I've heard a lot about you.
东西拿来看看
Break out the ice.
搞一口
Take a bump.
别担心  我不是条子
No worries, man. I'm no cop.
我说搞一口
I said hit it.
好
All right.
这真TM爽翻了
This kicks like a mule with his balls wrapped in duct tape.
-哪弄来的  -我做的
- Where'd you get it? - I cooked it.
鬼扯
Bullshit!
你为谁干活
Who you working for?
不为谁
No one, man. I mean,
我有个制毒的搭档
I have a partner that I cook with,
就是这样
But that's it.
好吧
All right.
成交
We got a deal.
看吧  我就说屠库会带上你的
See? I told you Tuco would hook you up.
好
Cool.
我还没说价钱呢
I haven't said how much.
说吧  多少
All right. How much?
3万5一磅
35 large for the pound.
瞧  还差点
Well, you're a little light, ese.
没关系  别紧张  很好
It's all right. Don't sweat it. It's all good.
好了  你们可以滚了
It's good. Walk. Get out of here.
-那钱呢  -你会拿到的
- What about the money?  - You'll get it.
这是寄售
This is a consignment operation.
你要赊3万5吗
You want me to float 35 G's?
你不信我
You don't trust me?
不  不  不是那样的
No, no. Hey, it's not that, man.
只是  你知道  我不
It's just, you know, I don't...
我没这么做过生意
I don't do business that way.
见鬼  已经成交了
Tough shit! The deal is done!
你不是说这样行的吗
You said this was cool.
交钱拿货  先付钱
Get money for meth. Cash up front.
别说预付了  Tuco会给钱的
Don't front, dude. Tuco's good for it.
我可不用你这废柴来给我担保
I don't need your punk ass to vouch for me!
放开
Come on!
Oh, come on!
你给我拿来的货是挺纯
All right, you brought me some really clean crystal.
你想要预付款吗
Do you really want your money up front?
预付款
Up front.
除了我
Nobody moves crystal
没人能在南谷贩毒
In the South Valley but me, bitch!
早安  雨果
Good morning, Hugo.
不介意我叫你雨果吧  雨果
Don't mind if I call you Hugo... Hugo.
街上还从没有过这么多人
We've never had a crowd on the street like that.
那不是汉克姨父
Is that Uncle Hank?
他逮捕了阿楚莱塔先生
Uncle Hank's arresting Mr. Archuleta.
这是怎么回事
This doesn't make any sense to me at all.
我不明白
I don't understand.
我给你4个字  背景调查
I got two words for you: background check.
行了吗
How about that?
哟  哟  哟  148-3369
Yo, yo, yo. 148-3369,
代表阿尔布开克
Representing the ABQ.
何事  贱人
What up, biatch?
提示音后留话
Leave it at the tone.
你究竟跑哪去了  给我回电话
Where the hell are you? Call me back.
-沃尔特  -怎么
- Hey, Walt. - Yeah?
汉克要发牌了
Hank's about to deal.
好  我马上过去
Okay. I'll be right there.
瞧瞧这一轮是什么牌
All right. Let's see what the turn brings us.
你看起来不错啊  沃尔特
You're looking good, Walt.
气色好多了
Your color's better.
是吗  谢谢
Yeah? Thanks.
其实他现在吃的药物药性很强
He's actually on the pretty strong stuff now.
戴尔克沃利医生想劝他
Dr. Delcavoli's trying to talk him into
休息一段时间  但是
taking some time off from work, but...
其实我今早和卡门谈过了
Well, actually, I just talked to Carmen this morning,
他们在这几周会找个代课老师
And they're getting a substitute for a few weeks.
我还没来得及告诉你  抱歉
I just didn't have a chance to tell you. Sorry.
该你下注  硬汉
Your bet, tough guy.
看牌
Check.
Yeah. Check.
都看牌
Check's in the mail.
1千万
10 million.
红的是2千5百万  蓝的才是1千万
Red's 25 million. Blue's 10.
那就2千5百万好了  我就这么玩
Then 25 million because that's how I roll.
汉克姨父  那天你为什么
Hey, Uncle Hank, why were you arresting
要逮捕阿楚莱塔先生
Mr. Archuleta the other day?
他人不错
He's a pretty cool guy.
可他有前科
Well, turns out that he has a record.
两次非法占有
Yeah. Couple of possession beefs.
我们查出就是他
We figure he was the guy
偷了你学校的化学实验器材
That was stealing your school's chemistry gear.
他有钥匙
I mean, you know, he had a key.
符合特征
Fit the profile.
我们搜了他的车
When we searched his truck,
找到个卷了大麻的大雪茄
We found a big old fat blunt,
这说明大个子雨果不是什么好人
which goes to prove old Huge Hugo ain't so cool after all.
到你了  沃尔特
It's to you, Walt.
跟注
Yeah, I'll call.
真不敢不相信
I can't believe the school system
学校竟不知道这家伙有前科
Didn't know about this guy's record.
真可怕
I mean, that's pretty scary.
他是怎么混进去的
How could something like that just slip through the cracks?
我不知道  不管怎样
I don't know. I mean, for what it's worth,
我觉得雨果根本不像是个会偷东西的人
Hugo just doesn't strike me as the thief.
沃尔特  这和个人感情无关
Yeah, well, nothing personal, Walt, but
你哪能一眼看出
You wouldn't know a criminal
谁是罪犯
if he was close enough to check you for a hernia.
也就是说  我们搞到了搜查令
Now, that said, we got a search warrant,
然后端了雨果的老窝
And we tore old Hugo's house apart.
原来他也是个瘾君子
Turns out he's a major league pothead.
但他那没有你的化学仪器
But he didn't raid your chemistry set.
赶紧出牌
You hiding something?
我跟
I'm in.
接着是底牌
And the river card.
牌不行  我不跟了
Yeah, I got nothing. I'm out.
赞
Yowsa!
当漏财大姐都不跟的时候
When old "holes in her purse" bails,
你就该知道你已经无路可退了
You know you're in deep.
就剩你跟我了  伙计
Looks like it's you and me, buddy.
雨果接下来会怎么样
What's going to happen to him? Hugo.
应该是丢了工作吧
Well, I mean, he's going to lose his job,
他活该的
Like he should.
没准还会在牢里呆几个月
Probably spend a couple months in County,
他也不是第一次了
As it's not his first rap.
我还等着呢
I'm waiting.
你是负隅顽抗呢
You going to man up,
还是缴械投降
Or you're going to puss out?
汉克
Hank.
啥  不好意思
What? Sorry.
全跟
I'm all in.
你可是大大的坏啊  你个骗子
You bad, bad, bad, horrible liar.
放烟雾弹呢哈
What are you smoking there, huh?
拿着带心牌了吧
You got a heart?
是红心 对不对
You got the flush, don't you?
才不上你的套儿  哥们  我扔牌
Nope. Not falling for it, buddy. I fold.
真够扫兴的
Talk about anti-climactic.
你牌不可能那么坏的
Your cards couldn't have been that bad.
天啊  老A你都扔了
Oh, my God. You threw away an ace...
你这是干嘛呢  不会吧
What are you doing? Don't.
还有张老K  就为了
...And a cowboy, for...
这个破牌
A handful of nothing.
是谁啊
Who is this?
我找的是杰西·平克曼
I was dialing Jesse Pinkman.
那么他上哪去了
Well, where is he, then?
你就是那谁吧
You the guy?
是  我就是
Yeah, I'm the guy.
他情况怎么样
How is he?
还能咋样  断了几根肋骨
Got some busted ribs and like that.
真是败得可以
Got messed up pretty good.
我一直劝屠库别打太狠
I was all like "Damn, Tuco, chill, ese."
真不知道他是吃错了哪门子药
I don't know what got into him. Seriously.
他还昏着呢  深度昏迷
Oh, he's out, man, way out.
还得持续上一段时间
They got him doped up big-time.
那么  货都是你造的吗
So you're the cook, huh?
喂  我还不知道你名呢
Yo, I didn't catch your name.
给我说说这个屠库
Tell me about this Tuco.
把他一切都告诉我
Tell me everything about him.
早上好
Good morning.
麻烦给我递下黄油
Would you pass the butter, please?
秃头够衰的  老爸
Bad ass, Dad.
你就是屠库
You Tuco?
我要跟屠库谈谈
I want to talk to Tuco,
见不到他我就不走
And I'm not leaving until I do.
你叫什么
What's your name?
海森堡
Heisenberg.
坐  海森堡
Have a seat, Heisenberg.
我不会在这呆太久
I don't imagine I'll be here very long.
不会太久
No?
好吧
All right.
那就站着吧
Be that way.
是你要会面的
It's your meeting.
为什么不先说说
Why don't you start talking
你想要什么
And tell me what you want?
5万块
$50,000.
哈  哥们  5万块
Oh, man! 50 G's?
你怎么想出来的
How you figure that?
3万5支付你抢走的货
35 for the pound of meth you stole
剩下的1万5
and another 15
用来补偿我同伙受的伤
for my Partner's pain and suffering.
同伙
Partner.
啊  想起来了  那个小贱人
Oh, yeah. I remember that little bitch.
那你就是他老爹了
So you must be Daddy.
让我理下思路啊
Let me get this straight.
我抢了你的货  是吧
I steal your dope, hmm?
狠揍了那小子一顿
I beat the piss out of your mule boy!
然后你又带着更多的货
And then you walk in here,
到我这来了
And you bring me more meth?
这想法真是赞
That's a brilliant plan, ese.
超赞
Brilliant.
有一点你说错了
You got one part of that wrong.
这不是冰毒
This is not meth.
这个死疯子
Are you fucking nuts?
你还想见识下
You want to find out?
别开枪  停下来
No-Doze, Gonzo, calma!
淡定  要淡定
Calma. Calma.
你真有种
You got balls.
我给你钱
I'll give you that.
行了吧
All right. All right.
我把钱给你
I'll give you your money.
你同伙上次带过来的货
That crystal that your partner brought me,
卖得比跟10块钱的站街女
It sold faster
打一炮的速度还要快
Than $10 ass in TJ.
也就是说  下星期
What say you bring me
你再给我带一磅过来吧
Another pound next week?
一手交钱一手交货
Money up front.
成交
All right.
一手交钱  一手交货
Money up front.
有时候  为了赚钱
Sometimes you got to rob
也不得不抢一点
To keep your riches.
这是我们靠长期实践得出的真理
Just as long as we got an understanding.
1磅不卖
One pound is not going to cut it.
要买就得买2磅
You have to take two.
成交
Orale.
这是什么鬼玩意
What is that shit?
雷酸汞盐
Fulminated mercury.
再掺合点化学改造
A little tweak of chemistry.